born.com 2011-06-06

# Welcome to Born

## Privacy Policy

    We are Born UK Limited (trading as BornForSports), Born FRANCE, 55 rue Pierre Charron, 75008 Paris. Company registration number: 6030412.

Your Privacy
    By accessing or using the Born Web site, you agree to the terms of the Born Ltd Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. 

Collection of Personal Information
    When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering, ordering products, or entering contests, Born may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, Born may require that you provide us personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number.
    When you submit personal information to Born you understand and agree that Born and its subsidiaries, affiliates and trusted vendors may transfer, store, and process your customer profile in any of the countries in which Born and its affiliates maintain offices, including without limitation, the United Kingdom.
    Born collects this information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you order a product, for example, the information is used to mail to you the items ordered and to provide you with any benefits that may be made available to registered users. If you enter a contest, information is collected to qualify the entry and contact you regarding the contest or prize awards. Born also uses information that you provide as part of our effort to keep you informed about special offers, and other Born products and services.
    Born recognises and appreciates the importance of responsible use of this information. If you do not want the information you provide to Born to be used to inform you of other products and special offers from Born, and you indicate this preference when you provide the information to us, we will honour your preference. In addition, Born may selectively provide certain information to other companies or organisations that have products or services we think may interest you. If you do not want the information you provide to Born to be shared with other companies, and you indicate this preference when you provide the information to us, we will honour your preference.
    Your personal information is password-protected to prevent unauthorised access to it. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone.

Use of Cookies
    When you visit Born, you can surf the site anonymously and access important information without revealing your identity. However, in order to provide better service, we may use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is a small piece of information that the Web site stores on your Web browser and can later retrieve. We use cookies for a number of administrative purposes, such as recording your log in status so you do not have to log in to the site at every visit (unless you wish to).
    The cookie cannot be read by a Web site other than the one that sent the cookie.
    While Born uses cookies to track your visit, most cookies last only through a single session or visit. Similarly this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided Born with personal information. Please note that it is possible to set up your Web browser to inform you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

Security Concerns
    Born is committed to ensuring that our customers have no security problems with the Born4sport.com website. Our research, however, has discovered one potential problem that our customers should be aware of. This is not a problem with the Born website and will affect all web sites that use Comodo Security, but only users with Netscape Communicator versions 4.05 and earlier and Microsoft Internet Explorer 4.01 for Macintosh will be affected by this problem.
    When you have added an item to your basket and started the purchase process, you are taken to the secure area of Born (a small padlock will be displayed at the bottom of your browser to indicate this). If you are a user of one of the browsers listed above you may receive a message box stating 'Certificate Authority Is Expired'. Born Ltd secure certificate has not expired and the error is simply a user interface error - there will be no problem with the actual security of the site or the encryption of your data.
    It is recommended that you update your browser to the latest version available by using the links below. If you do not wish to download the latest browser you can simply click 'continue' when you see the message 'Certificate Authority Is Expired'. As mentioned above the SSL session that secures your transaction with our site is not affected - your data will still be encrypted. You can avoid the dialog box in the future by upgrading your browser
    If you need any further help with this please email us at [customerservice-uk@born.com](mailto:customerservice-uk@born.com), or visit the help section to read more about Security on the born website. 

Removal of Personal Information
    You have the right to remove your personal information and preferences. In order to do this please write to us at: 
    Born FRANCE  
55 rue Pierre Charron

75008 Paris

    Please include your name, address, and/or the e-mail address you registered with when you contact us.
    Please note that Born is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Born Web sites to which Born may link.
